[{"difficulty":"MEDIUM","syllabus":"Module 1: Variables, Module 2: Methods, Module: When to Use Classes","comments":[{"replies":[{"comment":"I agree with your comment!","user":"05691ad3-8131-4ace-83cb-479cb636bcf9"}],"comment":"This was a really helpful introduction to classes!","user":"05691ad3-8131-4ace-83cb-479cb636bcf9"}],"reviews":[{"rating":4.76,"comment":"Really well written, had fun taking this course!","user":"a2f7d011-e206-42f5-9966-553e577976ac"}],"author":"a99d0e66-3539-43bf-a30c-7c11d8e6ef93","name":"Classes for Beginners","rating":4.33,"description":"Teaches how to create a class with variables and methods, then describes when to use a class.","students":[{"id":"a3d4c812-17bc-4e1d-bcae-442b556e63f5","grades":[100,50,60,90,70]}],"language":"PYTHON","id":"a1eb2fcc-761c-43e6-a743-c0780eebb3a8","modules":[{"comments":[{"replies":[{"comment":"I agree with your comment!","user":"05691ad3-8131-4ace-83cb-479cb636bcf9"}],"comment":"This was a really helpful introduction to classes!","user":"99fe4f2b-4832-40c4-a040-223286ee3cb5"}],"name":"Variables","lesson":[{"quiz":[],"title":"When to Use Classes: Variables","content":"A class is used when you have an object that has several traits. For example, if you were making a program for a dog shelter, a Dog would be a good class to make so that someone can log the dog into the shelter's system. The class would contain the dog's name, breed, and age. These would be established as variables. So when you create an instance of a dog, or in other words want to add a dog, you will need to enter a name, breed, and age. Since the class is created, you can make instances of as many dogs as you need to."},{"quiz":[{"question":"whgat","answers":["asdklf","asdfjik","nasdfa","none"],"correctAnswer":2}],"title":"Test","content":"Testing lesson"}]}]},{"difficulty":"EASY","syllabus":"Module 1: Course Introduction. Module 2: Python Basic. Module 3: Strings part 1. Module 4: Functions. Module 5: Flow Control. Module 6: Loops. Module 7: Strings part 2. Module 8: Methods. Module 9: Lists. Module 10: Dictionaries. Module 11 End of Course.","comments":[],"reviews":[],"author":"70393005-8896-430a-91e1-e5d8dcce54c1","name":"Zero to Hero: Python Bootcamp","rating":0.0,"description":"Learning Python like a Professional Start from the basics and go all the way to creating your own applications and games!","students":[],"language":"PYTHON","id":"d71e4051-a245-4167-b85e-9b09232e84c6","modules":[{"comments":[],"name":"Course Introduction","lesson":[{"quiz":[],"title":"Why python?","content":"Learn why you should learn Python and what you can use it for"}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Python Basic","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"How do you define a variable that equals 5?","answers":["num = 5;","num = 5","int num = 5; ","let num = 5;"],"correctAnswer":1}],"title":"Variable and Assignment","content":"Learn why you should learn Python and what you can use it for"},{"quiz":[{"question":"What is a boolean and how do you define it?","answers":["It is a whole number data type and can be defined as x = 5.","It is a real number data type and can be defined as x = 4.75.","Is is a collection of number, letters, and symbols data type and can be defined as x = \u2018Hello World\u2019","It is a logical data type and can be defined as x = true."],"correctAnswer":3}],"title":"Basic Data Type","content":"Basic Data Types in python include Integers, Floating-point numbers, Strings, Boolean, and Math functions. An Integer is a positive or negative whole number. You can define and variable to be an integer by saying \u201Cx = 5.\u201D A floating-point number is a real number with a decimal point. To define it you can say \u201Cx2 = 4.75\u201D and that will make x2 equal to 4.75. A string is a collection of characters like letters, numbers, and symbols. To define a string say \u201Cy = \u2018George\u2019.\u201D A boolean is a data type that only takes in and can only be defined with true or false. There are several math functions in Python such as math.cbrt(x) which would cube x."},{"quiz":[{"question":"How do you multiple in python?","answers":["x=5   y=5  z= x+y","int z = 5 * 7;","let z = 5 + 7;","None of the above"],"correctAnswer":0}],"title":"Comments and Arithmetic Operators","content":"Commenting in python is the inclusion of short descriptions along with the code to increase its readability. You can comment by saying \u201C#comment\u201D. Arithmetic operators include addition(+), subtraction(-), multiplication(*), division(\/), modulus(%), exponentiation(**), and floor division(\/\/). You would add by define two variables and adding then with \u2018+\u2019. For example, x is equal to 2 and y is equal to 4. To add them you would say \u201Cz = x + y\u201D. You will also do this for the other operation."},{"quiz":[{"question":"How do you print \u201CHello World\u201D in python? ","answers":["print(\u201CHello World\u201D)","System.out.println(\u201CHello World\u201D);","cout << \u201CHello World\u201D","print(\u201CHello World);"],"correctAnswer":0}],"title":"Printing","content":"Printing in python is when you print to the terminal or console so the user can see. You would use the command print()."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Strings part 1","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"What will be the output of this? Prime_numbers = [2,3,5,7]  type(Prime_numbers)","answers":["<class \u2018dict\u2019>","<class \u2018list\u2019>","<class \u2018_main_.Foo\u2019>","None of the above"],"correctAnswer":1}],"title":"type()","content":"The type() function is used to get the type of an object. It will either return the type of the object or return a new type object based on the arguments passed. Python type() function syntax is: type(object)."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Functions","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"What are the two types of functions in python?","answers":["If else statements and for loops?","Strings and integers","Standard library and user defined","None of the above"],"correctAnswer":2}],"title":"Types of Functions","content":"A function is a block of code that performs a specific task. There are two types of function in python programming. The first is the standard library functions  which are built-in functions in Python that are available to use. The second is a user-defined functions that the user create based on their requirements."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Flow Control","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"What is the code for: if the number is greater than 0, then print out number is positive?","answers":["if (number > 0) { print(\u2018Number is positive.\u2019); }","if number > 0: print(\u2018Number is positive.\u2019)","if (number > 0) :  print(\u2018Number is positive.\u2019);","None of the above"],"correctAnswer":1}],"title":"If Else Statements ","content":"In python, there are three different forms of an id statement: if, if else, and if elif else. The syntax of the statement is : if condition: #statement. The if statement evaluates condition in two ways: if condition is evaluated to true, the code inside of if is executed. The other way is if  condition is false, the code will skip to the else statement or whatever is outside of the if statement."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Loops","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Why do we need loops in programming?","answers":["For iterations","For traversals","To avoid repeating code","All the above"],"correctAnswer":3},{"question":"What is a correct syntax for a for loop in python?","answers":["for (initialExpression; textExpression; updateExpression) {#statement}","for val in sequence: #statement","for sequence in statement: #val","for statement in val: #sequence"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Which of the following is used when we want to exit a loop?","answers":["Continue","Exit","Break","Stop "],"correctAnswer":2}],"title":"For Loops","content":"We use loops in programming because they are transversals, iterations and can be used to avoid repeating code. There are two types of loops in python: for loops and while loops. This lesson will talk about a for loop. In Python a for loop is used to run a block of code for a certain number of times. It is used to iterate over any sequences such as list, tuple, string, etc. The syntax of the for loop would be this: for val in sequence: #statement. Val will be your variable that you want. The sequence is the list of things that you want to go through. Statement will be in the body of the for loop and will do what you want to do with the list."},{"quiz":[{"question":"What is the correct syntax for ta while loop in python?","answers":["while val in condition: #body","while(condition){#body}","while condition: #body","while body: #condition"],"correctAnswer":2}],"title":"While Loops","content":"Python while loop is used to run a block code until a certain condition is met. The syntax of a while loop is: while condition: # body. The while loop evaluates the condition. If the condition is true, the code inside the while loop is executed. The condition is evaluated again till the condition is false, then the loop stops. An example would be i = 1, n =5. while i <= n: print(i)  i=i+1. The output of this would be 1 2 3 4 5. The loop is terminated when i got to be bigger than 5."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Strings part 2","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"What would len() return in this code? days = [\u201CTuesday\u201D, \u201CThursday\u201D, \u201CFriday\u201D]   len(days)","answers":["Tuesday, Thursday, Friday","days","3","All the above"],"correctAnswer":2}],"title":"len()","content":"The len() function returns the number of items in an object. When the object is a string, the len() function returns the number of characters in the string."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Methods ","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"What is a method?","answers":["It is a label that you can call on an object","Is is a collection of number, letters, and symbols data type","It is a loop that can be used in a number of ways","None of the above."],"correctAnswer":0}],"title":"What is a method?","content":"A Python method is a label that you can call on an object; it is a piece of code to execute on that object. A method belongs in a class and it will take in a parameters."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Lists","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"What are the three types of lists?","answers":["String, integers, floats","If else, for, while","Tuple, set, dictionary","Standard library, user defined, program made"],"correctAnswer":2}],"title":"What is a list and what types are there?","content":"Lists are used to store multiple items in a single variable. Lists are one of 4 built-in data types in Python used to store collections of data, the other 3 are Tuple, Set, and Dictionary, all with different qualities and usage."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"Dictionaries","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"What is the dictionary syntax? ","answers":["dict = [object, object]","dict = [\u201Cobject\u201D: \u201Cobject\u201D]","dict = {object, object}","dict = { \u201Cobject\u201D: \u201Cobject\u201D}"],"correctAnswer":3}],"title":"Introduction to dictionaries","content":"Dictionary is a type of lists and they are used to store data values in key:value pairs."}]},{"comments":[],"name":"End of Course.","lesson":[{"quiz":[{"question":"How do you define a variable that equals 5?","answers":["num = 5;","num = 5","int num = 5; ","let num = 5;"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"What is the dictionary syntax? ","answers":["dict = [object, object]","dict = [\u201Cobject\u201D: \u201Cobject\u201D]","dict = {object, object}","dict = { \u201Cobject\u201D: \u201Cobject\u201D}"],"correctAnswer":3},{"question":"What is a method?","answers":["It is a label that you can call on an object","Is is a collection of number, letters, and symbols data type","It is a loop that can be used in a number of ways","None of the above."],"correctAnswer":0},{"question":"What is a boolean and how do you define it?","answers":["It is a whole number data type and can be defined as x = 5.","It is a real number data type and can be defined as x = 4.75.","Is is a collection of number, letters, and symbols data type and can be defined as x = \u2018Hello World\u2019","It is a logical data type and can be defined as x = true."],"correctAnswer":3},{"question":"What will be the output of this? Prime_numbers = [2,3,5,7]  type(Prime_numbers)","answers":["<class \u2018dict\u2019>","<class \u2018list\u2019>","<class \u2018_main_.Foo\u2019>","None of the above"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"How do you print \u201CHello World\u201D in python? ","answers":["print(\u201CHello World\u201D)","System.out.println(\u201CHello World\u201D);","cout << \u201CHello World\u201D","print(\u201CHello World);"],"correctAnswer":0},{"question":"What are the two types of functions in python?","answers":["If else statements and for loops?","Strings and integers","Standard library and user defined","None of the above"],"correctAnswer":2},{"question":"What is the code for: if the number is greater than 0, then print out number is positive?","answers":["if (number > 0) { print(\u2018Number is positive.\u2019); }","if number > 0: print(\u2018Number is positive.\u2019)","if (number > 0) :  print(\u2018Number is positive.\u2019);","None of the above"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"What is a correct syntax for a for loop in python?","answers":["for (initialExpression; textExpression; updateExpression) {#statement}","for val in sequence: #statement","for sequence in statement: #val","for statement in val: #sequence"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"What would len() return in this code? days = [\u201CTuesday\u201D, \u201CThursday\u201D, \u201CFriday\u201D]   len(days)","answers":["Tuesday, Thursday, Friday","days","3","All the above"],"correctAnswer":2}],"title":"Test","content":"This will be a test of all of the content that you have learned in this Course. You will need at least 70% to pass the course and get your certification. Good Luck!"}]}]}]